Boss! Boss!
Man, are you open or what, boss?
Yeah, we're open!
Then hurry up and open the door!
Bring out something steamy!
Something exciting!
Don't play that cut-in-half crap from last time.
Where are the tapes?
Coming!
These are the ones you guys usually like.
Take 'em and put 'em on yourselves.
Who's going to pay up?
No messing around today, huh?
Brother Xiaoguan,
where did you go yesterday?
The video parlor was closed all day.
I thought you skipped town.
Your video parlor is going under.
You've gotta change things up.
Otherwise it'll definitely go bust.
Nobody watches decent movies anymore.
You've gotta get explicit.
Japanese,
American,
North American.
I've got stock of all of it.
All in HD.
For real.
North American?
America is North America.
I know that.
America, North America, whatever.
You... you still owe me 500 yuan.
Remember?
It's been three months.
I didn't ask for interest.
I'm not pressing you, either.
I'm just saying, I've been decent, right?
But I really have no money right now.
How about this, then?
Tomorrow,
come with me.
A trip to the coast.
To pick up stock.
RAM sticks.
Worth a fortune.
How about it?
I'm scared of checkpoints alone, but you...
know the roads well.
You back me up.
That'll put my mind at ease.
If this goes through,
we settle the debt.
What do you think?
Fine.
Okay.
Deal.
You promised.
Settle the debt.
Don't be late tomorrow morning.
You're a pal.
Settle the debt.
Yeah, settle the debt.
I keep my word.
Don't be late tomorrow morning.
I'll come pick you up.
This is it, right?
Should be.
Go see what's going on first.
I gotta have a backup plan.
Let's go.
Huang?
That's me.
Thanks for making the trip.
Long trip getting here, huh?
Far.
It's pretty out of the way.
Here, have a smoke.
Appreciate it, brother.
No, thanks.
Let's hurry and check the goods, alright?
We've got plenty of goods, don't worry.
It's all top-notch stuff.
It's on the boat. Let's go, get on board.
Are there a lot of buyers today?
Oh, definitely.
Let me tell you,
if we weren't tight,
you wouldn't even lay eyes on this batch.
But let me tell you upfront,
RAM sticks are in crazy demand lately.
I can only give you a portion.
Can't give you too much.
Wait, don't do that, brother.
Come on, Old Yang, come over here.
It wasn't easy for me to make the trip.
Hook me up with a bit more, will you?
The good stuff is on the boat. Let's go pick it, alright?
We'll pick the best ones.
Come on, get on the boat.
Come on, Old Yang, get up there.
Brother.
Come on, board the boat, get on board.
You go first.
Come on.
Huang, you get on too. Up, up!
Easy, watch your step.
Come on.
You get on too.
Master Yang,
take us over to the big ship.
Sure thing.
Careful, brother. Watch your head.
Boss, we're here to pick up the goods.
Pick up what? On your knees!
There must be a misunderstanding!
We're just here for the RAM sticks.
Wait, didn't we just come over...
On your knees!
What the hell are you doing?
Who do you think you're shoving?
Kneel!
Twenty thousand.
Consider it your boat fare.
Twenty thousand yuan
is my life.
You guys seem honest enough.
As for this...
take it as your travel expenses.
Can you swim?
Jump.
Jump where?
Uh...
Got it, got it! Bro, bro, bro, jump!
Got it, got it, boss! Jump!
Thanks, boss!
Take it.
Thanks, bro.
Nearly got me killed.
People online are totally unreliable, bro.
I'm never trusting anyone online again.
You've never died before.
You don't know how good it is to be alive.
What did you say?
Let's go.
I keep my word.
Consider our debt settled.
Still making a scene with me?!
You think I know nothing?
Fucking slut!
Bro, bro, bro!
You bastard!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
What happened?
You get your ass—
What is it, bro?
Get your ass over here!
What are you doing?
Bro, bro, bro!
I'll strangle you!
Bro!
Bro, bro, bro!
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Who is it?
I'm back, I—
What's wrong?
You're here, huh?
Get up, get up!
I'm here.
Perfect.
Don't move! Don't you move!
Are you done yet?!
Shut up!
I said— I—
I'll beat this adulterer first,
then I'll deal with this whore!
What the hell are you saying?
Talk! Spit it out!
Bro, bro, bro!
When did this start?
Was it after I got to work?
I already...
caught you in the office!
Enough!
I'll talk!
What are you doing, bro?
It's been over between us for a long time!
Bro, bro, bro!
Fine, fine.
Get out of here!
Okay.
You slut!
Bro, bro, bro!
Just go!
Bro!
Don't you leave!
Get over here!
Have a drink with me.
Why are you holding a hammer to drink?
Wasn't it to scare that broad?
Well, you scared me instead.
Come on, little brother. Have a drink with me.
Where are my shoes?
Right here.
That crazy bitch...
Sit.
She really ran you ragged.
You introduced me to this...
Brother Liang's place, and in just a few days...
Barely a few days,
and I saw her in his...
Boss Liang's office.
All right.
Fuck.
When I went back,
everyone...
Everyone knew about it.
I went to confront him.
Two bodyguards.
One pinned my head to the floor.
I can take being a cuckold,
but don't boil me like a turtle, all right?
Bro, you're stupidly adorable.
Bro.
No way.
I know you've got connections.
Promise me one thing.
Shoot.
Help me...
get one of these.
Are you drunk out of your mind?
That's illegal!
Why would you mess with that?
You have a drop of booze
and forget who you are, huh?
I can be a cuckold.
I know I'm useless right now.
But you can't hit me!
Right.
We gotta kill him.
Damn right.
Kill him. Fuck him up.
We gotta kill him.
Come on, sit. Sit down, sit down.
Sit, sit.
Wait, no.
Let me tell you something else.
That bitch...
he wasn't the first.
Definitely not the first.
That bitch...
definitely...
had others before him.
Sure, fine, okay.
I just haven't found them.
Let's just drink, you and me.
Get some rest early.
We'll figure something out tomorrow, okay?
Figure what out?
Figure out how to kill him, okay?
Can't you just...
stop smoking already?
Can we open a window for fresh air?
I'm full of rage!
I'm boiling with rage right now!